Finding Aid for the Republic Pictures Corporation Records LSC.0979
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Continuity Scripts
  - A Gentle Gangster., 1942.; 4 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: Barton MacLane, Molly LaMont, Jack LaRue, Dick Wessel
  - Out California Way., 1946.; 4 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Adrian Booth
  - The Wayward Girl., 1957.; 2 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: Marcia Henderson, Peter Walker, Katharine Barrett
  - Web of Danger., 1947.; 4 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: Adele Mara, Bill Kennedy, Damian O'Flynn, Richard Loo
  - Woman Doctor., 1939.; 2 copies. (Box 13)
    Cast: Frieda Inescort, Henry Wilcoxon, Claire Dodd
  - Woman of the North Country., 1952.; 1 copy. (Box 13)
    Cast: Ruth Hussey, Rod Cameron, John Agar, Gale Storm
  - Savage Frontier (trailer - 20)., 1953.; 4 copies. (Box 14)
    Director: Harry Keller-
    Cast: Allan Rocky Lane, Eddy Waller
  - Billy the Kid and Geronimo., 1954.; 1 copy. (Box 14)
  - Thunder over Arizona., 1956.; 1 copy. (Box 14)
    Cast: Skip Homeier, Kristine Miller, George MacReady
  - Rustlers on Horseback., 1950.; 4 copies. (Box 14)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Roy Barcroft, Claudia Barrett
    - Rustlers on Horseback. (trailer)., 1950; 17 copies.
  - Marshal of Laredo., 1945.; 7 copies. (Box 14)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Bobby Blake, Alice Fleming, Peggy Stewart
  - Renegades of Sonora., 1948.; 18 copies. (Box 14)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Roy Barcroft, Frank Fenton
  - Rustlers of Devil's Canyon., 1947.; 10 copies. (Box 14)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Bobby Blake
  - Redwood Forest Trail., 1950.; 4 copies. (Box 14)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Jeff Donnell
  - Red River Renegades., 1946.; 5 copies. (Box 14)
    Cast: Sunset Carson, Peggy Stewart
  - Outlaws of Sonora., 1938.; 14 copies. (Box 14)
  - Clay Allison and Ben Thompson (Stories of the Century). CUT, 5 copies. (Box 14)
  - Clay Allison and Benn Thompson (Stories of the Century)., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 14)
  - The Purple Vigilantes., 1938.; 3 copies. (Box 14)
    Director: Goerge Sherman
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ray Corrigan, Max Terhune, Joan Barclay
  - Raiders of Old California., 1957.; 5 copies. (Box 14)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Arleen Whelan, Faron Young, Marty Robbins
    - Raiders of Old California. (trailer)., 1957; 15 copies.
  - The Ghost Goes Wild., 1946.; 16 copies. (Box 15)
    Cast: James Ellison, Anne Gwynne, Edward Everett Horton
  - Woman They Almost Lynched., 1953.; 3 copies. (Box 15)
    Director: Allan Dwan
    Cast: John Lund, Brian Donlevy, Audrey Totter, Joan Leslie
  - King of the Rocket Men (serial) episodes 9,10., 1 ea. copies. (Box 15)
    - King of the Rocket Men (serial) episodes 9,10 (trailer)., 14 copies.
  - Don Juan's Night of Love., 1952.; 2 copies. (Box 15)
    Director: Mario Sldati
    Cast: Raf Vallonek, Silvana Pampanini
  - The Fighting Chance., 1955.; 3 copies. (Box 15)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Julie London
  - King of the Gamblers., 1948.; 1 copy. (Box 15)
    Cast: Janet Martin, William Wright
  - Fighting Coast Guard., 1951.; 7 copies. (Box 15)
    Cast: Brian Donlevy, Forrest Tucker
  - Doctor At Sea., 1955.; 7 copies. (Box 15)
    Director: Ralph Thomas
    Cast: Dirk Bogarde, Brenda de Banzie
  - Scandal Incorporated., 1955.; 2 copies. (Box 15)
    Director: Edward Mann
    Cast: Robert Hutton, Paul Richards
  - Red River Shore., 1953.; 9 copies. (Box 16)
    Director: Harry Kellen
    Cast: Rex Allen, Slim Pickens
  - Wild Horse Ambush., 1952.; 4 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: Michael Chapin, Eilene Janssen, James Bell, Richard Avonde
  - Overland Stage Raiders., 1938.; 2 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: John Wayne, Ray Corrigan
  - The Kansas Terrors., 1939.; 2 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Raymond Hatton
  - Raiders of Sunset Pass., 1943.; 4 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: Eddie Dew, Smiley Burnette
  - Fort Dodge Stampede., 1951.; 3 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Chubby Johnson
  - The Gallant Legion., 1948.; 3 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: William Elliott, Adrian Booth Bruce Cabot, Andy Devine
  - John Wesley Hardin and The Younger Brothers (Stories of the Century)., 1954.; 2 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle, Richard Webb, Paul Keast
  - Bordertown Trail., 1944.; 9 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: Smiley Burnette, Sunset Carson
  - El Paso Stampede., 1953.; 8 copies. (Box 16)
  - Stagecoach to Denver., 1946.; 5 copies. (Box 16)
  - Dakota Incident., 1956.; 1 copy. (Box 16)
    Director: Lewis R. Foster
    Cast: Linda Darnell, Dale Robertson
  - The Dakota Kid., 1951.; 13 copies. (Box 16)
    Director: Phillip Ford
    Cast: Michael Chapin, Eilene Janssen
  - Stranger At My Door., 1956.; 3 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: MacDonald Carey, Patricia Medina
  - Sam Bass and Frank and Jesse James (Stories of the Century)., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle Don Haggerty, James Anderson
  - Sheriff of Wichita., 1949.; 7 copies. (Box 16)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Black Jake (that Horse), Eddy Waller
  - Two Wise Maids., 1937.; 2 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Alison Skipworth, Polly Moran
  - The Wac from Walla Walla. (trailer - 15)., 1952; 2 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Judy Canova, Stephen Dunne
  - Juvenile Jungle., 1958.; 3 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Corey Allen, Rebecca Welles
  - The Red Menace., 1949.; 2 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Robert Rockwell, Hanne Axman, Betty Lou Gerson, Barbra Fuller
  - The Mandarin Mystery., 1936.; 5 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Eddie Quillan, Charlotte Henry, Rita La Roy
  - Stand-Up and Sing., 1946.; 3 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Constance Moore, William Marshall
  - Satan's Satellites., 1952.; 3 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Judd Holdren, Aline Towne, Wilson Wood, Lane Bradford
  - Romance On The Run., 1938.; 12 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Donald Woods, Patricia Ellis
  - The Twinkle In God's Eye., 1955.; 7 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Mickey Rooney, Coleen Gray
  - Come Next Spring., 1955.; 12 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Ann Sheridan, Steve Cochran, Walter Brennan, 1955
  - Gay Blades., 1946.; 20 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Jean Rogers, Edward Ashley, Frank Albertson
  - A Woman's Devotion., 1956.; 1 copy. (Box 17)
    Director: Paul Henreid
    Cast: Ralph Meeker, Janice Rule
  - Trouble in the Glen., 1954.; 6 copies. (Box 17)
    Cast: Margaret Lockwood, Orson Welles, Forrest Tucker, Victor McLaglen
  - The Crocked Circle., 1957.; 10 copies. (Box 18)
    Cast: John Smith, Fay Spain
  - The Congress Dances., 1955.; 3 copies. (Box 18)
    Director: Herbert J. Yates (p)
    Cast: Johanna Matz, Rudolf Prack
  - Dancing Feet., 1936.; 10 copies. (Box 18)
    Cast: Ben Lyon, Joan Marsh
  - Crazylegs., 1953.; 2 copies. (Box 18)
    Director: Francis D. Lyon
    Cast: Lloyd Nolan, Joan Vohs
  - Double Jeopardy., 4 copies. (Box 18)
    Cast: Rod Cameron
  - Federal Man-Hunt., 1938.; 6 copies. (Box 18)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, June Travis
  - Jungle Stampede., 1950.; 2 copies. (Box 18)
    Director: George Breadston
    Cast: George Breakston, Yorke Coplen
  - The Jungle Wilderness., 1948.; 2 copies. (Box 18)
    Cast: George Brent, Vera Ralston
  - Bullfighter and the Lady., 1951.; 8 copies. (Box 18)
    Cast: Robert Stack, Joy Page, Gilbert Roland, Virginia Grey
  - Lady For a Night., 1942.; 4 copies. (Box 18)
    Director: Leigh Jason
    Cast: Joan Blondell, John Wayne
  - The Divided Heart. (Box 18)
    Director: Charles Crichton
    Cast: Cornell Borchers, Yvonne Mitchell
    - Post-Production., 4 copies.
    - Continuity
    - Cutting., 3 copies.
    - Trailer., 6 copies.
    - Superimposed Spotted
    - List., 1954.; 3 copies.
  - A Strange Adventure., 1956.; 1 copy. (Box 19)
    Cast: Joan Evans, Ben Cooper
  - Stardust and Sweet Music. (trailer - 20)., 1947; 10 copies. (Box 19)
    Director: Allan Duan
    Cast: Jane Frazee, William Marshall
  - Gangs of the Waterfront., 1945.; 1 copy. (Box 19)
    Cast: Robert Armstrong, Stephanie Bachelor, Martin Kosleck
  - The President's Mystery., 1936.; 4 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Hanry Wilcoxon, Betty Furness
  - Romance and Rhythm., 1940.; 11 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Kenny Baker, Francis Langford
  - Steppin' In Society., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 19)
    Director: Alexander Esway
    Cast: Edward Everett Horton, Gladys George
  - The Saint Meets The Tiger., 1943.; 4 copies. (Box 19)
    Director: Paul Stern
    Cast: Hugh Sincliar, Jean Gillie
  - Forged Passport., 1939.; 2 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Paul Kelly, June Lang
  - Ladies Crave Excitement., 1935.; 2 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Normas Foster, Evalyn Knoapp
  - Journey To Freedom., 1957.; 2 copies. (Box 19)
    Director: Robert C. Dertano
    Cast: Jacques Scott, Geneviv Aumont
  - Carolina Cannonball., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Judy Canova, Andy Clyde, Ross Elliott
  - Carolina Cannonball. CUT, 1954.; 3 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Judy Canova, Andy Clyde, Ross Elliott, Sig Ruman
  - Angel on the Amazon., 1958.; 4 copies. (Box 19)
    - Angel on the Amazon. (trailer), 1958
  - Stars and Guitars., 1944.; 12 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Tito Guizar, Virginia Bruce, Edward Everette Horton
  - Stagecoach To Monterey., 1944.; 2 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Twinkle Watts, Allen Lane
  - Village Barn Dance., 1940.; 2 copies. (Box 19)
    Cast: Vera Vague, Doris Day
  - Black Hills Ambush., 1952.; 9 copies. (Box 20)
  - Beyond the Border., 1945.; 7 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: Tito Guizar, Constance Moore
  - The Big Bonanza., 1944.; 7 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: Richard Arlen, Robert Livingston
  - Alias Billy the Kid., 1946.; 10 copies. (Box 20)
  - Corpus Christi Bandits., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 20)
    Director: Wallace A. Grissell
    Cast: Allan Lane, Helen Talbot
  - Corpus Christi Bandits. CUT, 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Helen Talbot, Jack Kirk
  - The Texas Uprising., 1947.; 9 copies. (Box 20)
    Director: Edward Ludwig
    Cast: William Elliott, John Carroll, Andy Devine
    - The Texas Uprising. (trailer)., 1947; 16 copies.
  - Hell's Crossroads., 1957.; 12 copies. (Box 20)
    Director: Franklin Adreon
    Cast: Stephen McNally, Peggie Castle, Robert Vaughn
  - The Last Command., 1950.; 10 copies. (Box 20)
    Director: Frank Lloyd
    Cast: Sterling Hayden, Anna Maria Alberghetti, Ernest Borgnine
  - Sheriff of Cimarron., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: Sunset Carson, Linda Stirling
    - Sheriff of Cimarron. (trailer)., 1945; 26 copies.
  - Sheriff of Las Vegas., 1944.; 14 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Bovvy Blake, Alice Fleming, Peggy Stewart
  - Sheriff of Sundown., 1944.; 3 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: Allan Land, Linda Stirling Max Terhune, Twinkle Wetts
  - Stagecoach Express., 1942.; 1 copy. (Box 20)
    Cast: Don Barry, Lynn Merrick
  - Montana Belle., 5 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: Jane Russell and George Brent, Scot Brady, Forest Tucker
  - The Plunderers., 1948.; 4 copies. (Box 20)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Ilona Massey, Adrian Booth, Forrest Tucker
  - Pride of the Plains., 1943.; 2 copies. (Box 20)
    Director: Wallace Fox
    Cast: Bob Livingston, Smiley Burnette, Nancy Gay
  - Pride of the Plains. CUT, 1949.; 2 copies. (Box 20)
  - Midnight Melody., 1946.; 10 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Vera Ralston, William Marshall
  - Midnight Melody. CUT, 1946.; 1 copy. (Box 21)
    Cast: Vera Ralston, William Marshall, Helen Walker
    - Trailer., 10 copies.
  - Mexicana., 1945.; 2 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Tito Guizar, Constance Moore, Leo Carrillo
  - The Traitor Within., 1942.; 15 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Donald M. Barry, Jean Parker, George Cleveland
  - Pride of Maryland., 1950.; 5 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Stanley Clements, Peggy Stewart
  - Trocadero., 1944.; 6 copies. (Box 21)
    Director: William Night
    Cast: Rosemary Lane, Johnny Downs Ralph Morgan
  - A Sporting Chance., 1945.; 6 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Jane Randolph, John O'Malley
  - A Sporting Chance. CUT, 1945.; 13 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Jane Randolph, John O'Malley, Stephen Barclay, Edward Gargan
  - Strange Case of Dr. Manning., 1957.; 5 copies. (Box 21)
    Director: Arthur Crabtree
    Cast: Ron Randell, Greta Gynt
    - Strange Case of Dr. Manning. (trailer)., 1957; 6 copies. (Box 21)
  - The Shanghai Story., 1954.; 11 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Ruth Roman, Edmond O'Brien
  - The Wild Blue Yonder. CUT, 4 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Wendell Corey, Vera Ralston
    - The Wild Blue Yonder (trailer)., 1951.; 26 copies.
  - The Wild Blue Yonder., 1951.; 5 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Wendell Corey, Vera Ralston, Forrest Ticler, Phil Hariss
  - The Wild Blue Yonder. CUT, 1951.; 1 copy. (Box 2)
    Cast: Wendell Corey, Vera Ralston, Forest Tucker, Phil Harris
  - Street Bandits., 1951.; 12 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Penny Edwards, Robert Clarke
    - Street Bandits. (trailer)., 1951; 15 copies.
  - Three Faces West., 1940.; 1 copy. (Box 21)
    Cast: John Wayne, Charles Coburn, Helen MacKellar
  - Three Faces West. CUT, 1940.; 8 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: Charles Coburn
  - The Three Mesquiteers., 1936.; 11 copies. (Box 21)
    Director: Ray Taylor
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ray Corrigan, Syd Saylor
  - The Three Mesquiteers. CUT, 1936.; 2 copies.
  - The Fighting Seabees., 1944.; 16 copies. (Box 21)
    Cast: John Wayne, Susan Hayward, Dennis O'Keefe, William Frawley
  - The Fighting Devil Dogs., 1938.; 6 copies. (Box 22)
    Director: William Witney, John English
    Cast: Lee Powell, Herman Brix
  - Flame of the Islands., 1955.; 5 copies. (Box 22)
    Cast: Yvonne De Carlo, Howard Duff
  - Flame of the Islands. CUT, 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 22)
    Director: Edward Ludwid
  - The Flying Squadron., 1952.; 11 copies. (Box 22)
    Director: Luigi Capuano
    Cast: Massino Serato, Dina Sassoli
  - Forced Landing., 1935.; 2 copies. (Box 22)
    Director: Melville Brown
    Cast: Esther Ralston, Onslow Stephens
  - When Gangland Strikes., 1955.; 15 copies. (Box 22)
    Cast: Raymond Greenleaf, Marjie Millar
  - Lay That Rifle Down., 1955.; 18 copies. (Box 22)
    Cast: Judy Canova, Robert Lowery
    - Lay That Rifle Down. (Superimposed Spotted List - English copy)., 1955; 1 copy.
  - No Man's Woman., 1955. (Box 22)
    Cast: Marie Windson, John Archer, Patric Knowles, Naney Gates
  - No Man's Woman. CUT, 1955.; 6 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Marie Windsor, John Archer, Patric Knowles
  - No Man's Woman. CUT, 1955. (Box 22)
    Cast: Marie Windsor, John Archer, Petric Knowles, Nancy Oates
  - Missing Women., 1951.; 3 copies. (Box 22)
    Cast: Penny Edward, James Millican, John Gaulaudet
  - Moonlight Masquerade., 1942. (Box 22)
    Cast: Dennis O'Keefe, Jane Frazee, Betty Kean, Eddie Foy, Jr.
  - Mystery of the Black Jungle., 1954.; 11 copies. (Box 22)
    Director: Ralph Murphy
    Cast: Lex Barker, Jane Maxwell, Paul Muller, Jack Rex
  - Mystery of the Black Jungle. CUT, 1954. (Box 22)
    Cast: Lex Barker, Jane Maxwell, Luigi Tosi, Paul Muller
  - Mystery Broadcast., 1943.; 4 copies. (Box 22)
    Cast: Frank Albertson, Ruth Terry, Nils Asther, Wynne Gibson
  - Mystery Breadcast. CUT, 1943.; 5 copies. (Box 22)
    Cast: Frank Albertson, Ruth Ferry
  - My Buddy., 1944.; 8 copies. (Box 22)
    Cast: Donald Barry, Ruth Terry
  - My Buddy. CUT, 1944.; 7 copies. (Box 22)
    Director: Steve Sekely (!)
    Cast: Donald Barry, Ruth Terry, Alexander Granaeh, Emma Dunn
  - Secrets of the Underground., 1942 (Box 22)
    Director: William Morgan
    Cast: John Hubbard, Virginia Grey, Lloyd Corrigan
  - Someone to Remember., 1943 (Box 22)
    Cast: Mabel Paige, John Craven, Dorothy Morris
  - Calling All Marines., 1939.; 17 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Donald Barry, Helen Mack
  - City of Shadows., 1955.; 4 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Victor McLaglen, John Baer
  - Affairs of Jimmy Valentine., 1942.; 6 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Dennis O'Keefe, Ruth Terry
  - Affairs of Jimmy Valentine. CUT, 1942.; 1 copy. (Box 23)
    Cast: Dennis O'Keefe, Ruth Terry, Gloria Dickson, Roman Bohnen
  - The Fatal Witness., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Evelyn Ankers, Richard Fraser
  - The Fatal Witness. CUT, 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 23)
    Director: Leseley Selander
    Cast: Evelyn Ankers, Richard Frasher
  - The Wayward Girl., 1957.; 7 copies. (Box 23)
    Director: Lesley Slander
    Cast: Marcia Henderson, Peter Walker
  - Stormbound. CUT, 1941.; 6 copies. (Box 23)
    Director: Alessandro Cicognini
    Cast: Constance Dowling, Andrea Chechi
    - Stormbound. (trailer)., 1941; 26 copies.
  - Stormbound., 1941.; 4 copies. (Box 23)
    Director: Luigi Capuqno
  - Three's a Crowd., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Pamela Blake, Charles Gordon
  - Three's a Crowd. CUT, 1945.; 13 copies. (Box 23)
  - Too Late For Tears., 1949.; 9 copies. (Box 23)
    Director: Byron Haskin
    Cast: Elizabeth Scott, Donl DeFore
  - Angel On The Amazon., 1948.; 6 copies. (Box 23)
  - Bal Tabarin., 1952.; 10 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Muriel Lawrence, William Ching
  - An Angel Comes To Brooklyn., 1945.; 8 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Kaye Dowd, Robert Duke
  - An Angel Comes to Brooklyn. CUT, 1945.; 9 copies. (Box 23)
  - The Fighting Chance., 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 23)
  - City of Shadows., 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 23)
  - Daniel Boone, Trail Blazer., 1956.; 10 copies. (Box 23)
    Director: Albert C. Gannaway, Ismael Rodriguez
    Cast: Bruce Bennett, Lon Chaney
  - Circus Girl. CUT, 1955.; 5 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: Kristina Soederbaaum
  - Circus Girl., 1937.; 9 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: June Travis, Robert Livingston
  - Circus Girl. CUT, 1937.; 8 copies. (Box 23)
    Cast: June Travis, Robert Livingston, Donald Cook, Betty Compson
  - The Maverick Queen., 1956.; 5 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Barbara Stanwyck, Barry Sullivan, Scott Brady, Mary Murphy
    - The Maverick Queen. (trailer)., 1956; 7 copies.
  - The Denver Kid., 1948.; 10 copies. (Box 24)
  - Desert of Lost Men., 1941.; 10 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Irving Bacon
  - Vigilante Hidecut., 1950.; 4 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Eddy Waller, Virginia Herrick, Allan Lane
  - The Fabulous Señorita., 1952.; 19 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Estelita, Robert Clarke
  - Man or Gun., 1957.; 1 copy. (Box 24)
    Cast: MacDonald Carey, Audrey Totter, James Gleason
  - Man or Gun. CUT, 1957.; 1 copy. (Box 24)
    - Man or Gun. (trailer). CUT, 1957; 40 copies.
    - Man or Gun. (Superimposed Spotted List - English Copy). CUT, 1957; 6 copies.
  - Man or Gun. CUT, 9 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: MacDonald Carey, Audrey Totter.
  - Song of Mexico., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 24)
    Director: James A. Fitzpatrick
    Cast: Adele Mara, Edgar Barrier
  - Hidden Guns., 1955.; 5 copies. (Box 24)
    Director: Al Gannaway
    Cast: Bruce Bennett, Richard Arlen
  - Hidden Guns. CUT, 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Bruce Bennett, Richard Arlen, John Carradine
  - Heroes of the Hills., 1938.; 8 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ray Corrig
  - Vigilantes of Dodge City., 1944.; 9 copies. (Box 24)
  - Sun Valley Cyclone., 1946.; 2 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott
  - Iron Mountain Trail., 1953.; 2 copies. (Box 24)
    - Iron Mountain Trail. (trailer)., 1953; 16 copies.
  - Vigilantes of Boomtown., 1946.; 19 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Bobby Blake
  - South Pacific Trail., 1942.; 10 copies. (Box 24)
    - South Pacific Trail. (trailer)., 1942; 12 copies.
  - Code Of The Prairie., 1944.; 3 copies. (Box 24)
  - The Wyoming Bandit., 1949.; 4 copies. (Box 24)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Trevor Bardette
    - The Wyoming Bandit. (trailer)., 1949; 7 copies.
  - Strangers in the Night., 1944.; 13 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: William Terry, Virginia Grey
  - Strange Impersonation., 1955.; 4 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: Brenda Marshall William, Gargan H.B. Warner
  - That Brennan Girl., 1946.; 15 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: James Dunn, Mona Freeman
    - That Brennan Girl. (trailer)., 1946; 36 copies. (Box 25)
  - That's My Baby., 1944.; 2 copies. (Box 25)
    Director: William Burke
    Cast: Richard Arlen, Ellen Drew
  - Spoilers of the Forest., 1957.; 6 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Vera Ralston
  - Spoilers of the North., 1947.; 3 copies. (Box 25)
    Director: Richard Sale
    Cast: Paul Kelly, Adrian Booth
  - Ice-Capades., 1941.; 14 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: Dorothy Lewis, James Ellison
  - Hell Ship Mutiny., 1957.; 3 copies. (Box 25)
    Director: Lee Sholem and Elmo Williams
    Cast: Jon Hall, John Carradine Peter Lorre
  - In Old Vienna., 1956.; 2 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: Heinz Roettinger
  - In Old Vienna. CUT, 1956.; 10 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: Heinz Roettinger, Henriette Hiess, Robert Killick, Hanni Loser, Dr. Kurt Jaggberg, Marianne Schonauer
  - That's My Gal., 1946.; 5 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Donald Barry, Pinky Lee
    - That's My Gal. (trailer)., 1946; 1 copy.
  - Sons of Adventure., 1948.; 2 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Russ Hayden
  - SOS Tidal Wave., 1939.; 9 copies. (Box 25)
    Cast: Ralph Byrd, George Barbier
  - Happy Go Lucky., 1936.; 5 copies. (Box 25)
    Director: Aubrey Scotto
    Cast: Phil Regan, Evelyn Venable
  - Headline Hunters., 1955.; 1 copy. (Box 25)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Julie Bishop
  - Headline Hunters. CUT, 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 25)
  - Headline Hunters. CUT, 1955.; [Duplicate].; 3 copies. (Box -)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Julie Bishop, Ben Cooper
    - Headline Hunters. (trailer)., 1955; 30 copies.
  - False Faces., 1943.; 6 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: Stanley Ridges, Bill Henry
  - Affair In Reno., 1957.; 10 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: John Lund, Doris Singleton
  - Behind City Lights., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Peter Cookson
  - Atlantic City Honeymoon., 1944.; 10 copies. (Box 26)
    Director: Ray McCarey
    Cast: Constance Moore, Brad Taylor
  - A Song For Miss Julie., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 26)
    Director: William Rowland
    Cast: Shirley Ross, Jane Farrar
  - End of the Road., 1944.; 3 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: Edward Norris, John Abbott
  - Suicide Squadron., 1942.; 15 copies. (Box 26)
    Director: Brian Desmond Hurst
    Cast: Anton Walbrook, Sally Gray
  - Gobs and Gals., 1952.; 12 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: George and Bert Bernard
  - Born To Be Wild., 1938.; 3 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: Robert E. Keane, Bentley Hewlett
  - This is Korea., 6 copies. (Box 26)
    Director: U.S. Navy - prod.
    Cast: Documentary
  - Forged Passport., 1939.; 6 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: Paul Kelly, June Lang, Lyle Talbot, Billy Gilbert
  - Geraldine., 1953.; 10 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: John Carrol, Mala Powers, Jim Backus, Stan Freberg, Carolyn Jones
    - Geraldine. (trailer)., 1953; 15 copies.
    - Geraldine. (Superimposed Spotted List - English copy)., 1953; 1 copy.
  - Fugitive Lady., 1950.; 13 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: Janis Paige, Binnie Barnes
    - Fugitive Lady. (trailers)., 1950; 23 copies.
  - Streets of San Francisco., 1949.; 10 copies. (Box 26)
    Cast: Robert Armstrong, Mae Clarke
    - Streets of San Francisco (trailer)., 7 copies. (Box 26)
  - Street of Darkness., 1958.; 5 copies. (Box 26)
    Director: Robert Walker
    Cast: Robert Keys, John Close
  - The Sun Shines Bright., 1953.; 11 copies. (Box 26)
    Director: John Ford
    Cast: Charles Winninger, Stepin Fetchit, Jane Darwell, Mae Marsh
  - Specter of the Rose., 1946.; 2 copies. (Box 27)
    Director: Ben Hecht
    Cast: Judith Anderson, Michael Chekov
    - Specter of the Rose. (trailer)., 1946; 11 copies. (Box 27)
  - I Dream Of Jeanie., 1952.; 5 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Ray Middleton, Bill Shirley
  - It Could Happen to You., 1937.; 6 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Alan Baxter, Andrea Leeds
  - Havana Rose., 1951.; 11 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Estelita Rodriguez, Bill Williams, Hugh Herbert
  - Gentlemen from Louisiana., 1936.; 9 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Gordon Rigby, Joseph Fields
  - Missing Women., 1951.; 6 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Penny Edwards, James Millican
  - Make Haste To Live., 1954.; 6 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Dorothy McGuire, Stephen McNally, May Murphy